Guide to the Gay & Lesbian Advocates & Defenders Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Non-GLAD Publications, 1973-2006; Series V
  - Exler, Andrew Ros, Civil Rights Report, 1985 July (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Fanlight Productions - "First Dance", 1986 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Fantasia Fair, 1988-1989 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Fenway Community Health Center, 1985-1998 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Fine By Me, Undated (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - First City Network, Network News, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Fort Wayne Lambda Projects, The Torch, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Frameline, Circa 2005 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Franklin Pierce Law Center, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Free Sharon Kowalski, Circa 1988 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Freedom to Marry, 1997 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Fund for Human Dignity, 1988 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD), 1989-2005 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Gay and Lesbian Community Action Council (GLCAC), 1990 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Gay and Lesbian Independent School Teacher Network (GLISTeN), Undated (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Gay and Lesbian Parents Coalition International (GLPCI), 1987-1990 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Gay Community News, 1973, 1975, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Gay Fathers Forum, Circa 1987 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Gay Fathers of Toronto (GFT), 1986 June (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Gay, Lesbian and Bisexual Educators Coalition, 1986 January (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Gay Lesbian and Straight Education Network (GLSEN), 2002 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Gay, Lesbian and Straight Teachers Network (GLSTN), Circa 1997 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC), 1987-1997 (Box 87, Folder 17-18)
  - Gay Speakers Bureau, 1991 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Gay Veterans Association (GVA), Circa 1985 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Gay Weekly, 1976 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Gay Youth, Committee for, Undated (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Gender Public Advocacy Coalition (GPAC), 2004 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Girlspace, Undated (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Greater Boston Civil Rights Coalition, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Greater Boston Lesbian/Gay Political Alliance, 1994 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Hartford Gay and Lesbian Health Collective (HGLHC), Children from the Shadow, 1998-1999 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Harvard University, 1991, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Haymarket People's Fund, Haymarket News, 1984-1987 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Heterosexuality, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Hispanic AIDS Forum (HAF), Undated (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - HIV Hotline, 1993 January (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Hospice of Cambridge, 1988 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Houston's Gay Political Caucus (GPC), "Update", 1982 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Human Outreach and Achievement Institute, 1985-1989 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Human Rights Campaign Foundation, 2000, 2005, undated (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Human Rights Campaign Fund, Momentum, 1989-1991 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Human Rights Resource Center, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - I Know You Know, 1985 December (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - The Impact Record, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Institute for Gay and Lesbian Strategic Studies (IGLSS), 1996, 2002-2005 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Institute for the Protection of Lesbian and Gay Youth (IPLGY), 1986 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - International Gay and Lesbian Archives, 1986 May (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - It's Time Massachusetts (ITMA), 1997 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - J2CP, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Just Out, 2002 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1985-1997, 2000 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Lambda 10 Project, Circa 1993 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Latino Health Network, 1989 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Lawyers for Human Rights (LHR), 1983-1986 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Lesbian and Gay Community Services Center, Inc., Circa 1986 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Lesbian and Gay Law Association of Greater New York, Lesbian/Gay Law Notes, 1993-1995 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Lesbian and Gay Political Alliance of Massachusetts, Undated (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Lesbian Connection, 2002 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Lesbian Mothers' Defence Fund (LMDF), Grapevine, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Lesbian Mothers' National Defense Fund (LMNDF), 1985-1986, 1988, 1991 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Lesbian Rights Project (LRP), 1985-1987 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Lewiston Prison Project, Undated (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Lincoln Coalition for Gay and Lesbian Civil Rights, Undated (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Log Cabin Club, The Log, 1985 April (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Los Angeles Gay and Lesbian Community Services Center, 1987, 1991 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Love Makes a Family, Circa 2004 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Lutherans Concerned, 2005 October (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Lyon-Martin Women's Health Services, Undated (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Maine Lesbian/Gay Political Alliance (MLGPA), 1994 March (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Maine Lesbians, Gaymen, Bisexuals and Transgendered's Symposium, 1995-1996 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Mass Act Out, 1988 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Asian AIDS Prevention Project (MAAPP), 2002 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Bar Association, 1990-1991 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Coalition of Battered Women Service Groups, Undated (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Commission Against Discrimination (MCAD), Circa 1993 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Continuing Legal Education, Inc. (MCLE), 1985, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Correctional Legal Services, Inc. (MCLS), 1998 January (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Council for Public Justice (MCPJ), 1987 February (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Department of Public Health, 1984 March (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts English Plus Coalition, Undated (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Gay and Lesbian Political Caucus, 1989 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Gay Political Caucus, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology Women's Studies, Undated (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Law Reform Institute, 1994 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Senior Action Council, Undated (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Mayor's Commission on Affairs of the Elderly, Boston Seniority, 2005 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Memphis Gay Coalition, Gaze, 1989 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Men of Color Against AIDS (MOCAA), 1996-1997 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Metropolitan Community Church of Boston, 1989 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Michigan Organization of Human Rights (MOHR), 1987 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - "Mothers and Others, A Cabaret about Sexuality, Motherhood and Choice", Undated (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Multicultural AIDS Coalition, Undated (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - National Adoption Exchange (NAE), Undated (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - National AIDS Network, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - National Association of Black and White Men Together (NABWMT), 2005 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - National Association of Business Councils (NABC), 1984-1985 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - National Association of Gay and Lesbian Democratic Clubs, Gay Writes, 1985-1986 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - National Association of Organizations Working for Equal Justice, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - National Association of People w/AIDS (NAPWA), Alert Medical, 1993 May-June (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - National Center for Lesbian Rights (NCLR), 1990-1997 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - National Center on Women and Family Law (NCOWFL), The Women's Advocate, 1982 December-1983 September (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - National Coalition of Anti-Violence Programs (NCAVP), Circa 2004 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - National Committee for Responsive Philanthropy, 1986, 1989, 1991 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - National Community AIDS Partnership, 1992 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - National Conference, 1998, undated (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - National Conference on Lesbian and Gay Legal Issues, 1988 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - National Conference on Women and the Law, 1986 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - National Education Foundation for Individual Rights (NEFIR), Circa 1980 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - National Gay Alliance for Young Adults (NGAYA), 1988 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Domestic Violence Victims Network, Undated (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force (NGLTF), 1989-2005 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force (NGLTF), Task Force Report, 1982-1990 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - National Gay Rights Advocates (NGRA), 1978-1989 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases (NIAID), Clinical Courier, 1992 January (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - National Latino/a Lesbian and Gay Organization (LLEGO), 1994 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - National Lawyers Guild, Anti-Sexism Newsletter, 1985-1986, 1989 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - National Lawyers Guild, Mass Dissent, 1985-1988 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - National Lesbian and Gay Health Foundation (NLGHF), 1988-1990 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - National Lesbian and Gay Journalists Association (NLGJA), 1995 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - National Lesbian and Gay Law Association (NLGLA), 1993-1995, 2005 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - National Lesbian Conference, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - National Organization for Victim Assistance (NOVA), 1986-1987 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - National Organization for Women (NOW), 1983, undated (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - National Organization of Gay and Lesbian Scientists and Technical Professionals (NOGLSTP), 1986 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - National Prison Project of the American Civil Liberties Union, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Network for Battered Lesbians, Undated (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - New England Medical Center, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - New England Pride Guide, 1993 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - New England Women's Fund, New Fund Matters, 2002 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - New Hampshire Alliance for Gay and Lesbian Rights, Breathing Space, 1986-1989, 1993 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - New Hampshire Lesbian and Gay Pride, 1983 June (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - News of the Columbus Gay and Lesbian Community, 1982 May (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - North Carolina Human Rights Fund (NCHRF), Undated (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - North Shore AIDS Health Project (NSAHP), The Project News, 1993 December (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - North Shore Gay and Lesbian Alliance (NSGLA), 1986 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Northampton Pride, 2006 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Northeastern University School of Law, Undated (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Office of the Massachusetts Secretary of State, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - ONE-NH, Community News, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Options, 1995, 2006 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Our Paper, 1989 September (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Out in Montana, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Out in the Mountains, 1988-1993, 2002, 2005-2006 (Box 90, Folder 9-10)
  - Pacific School of Religion, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG), 1986, 1997 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Partners, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - People of Color Organizing Institute, Undated (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Pike Institute on Law and Disability, Boston University School of Law, Disability Advocates Bulletin, 1992 October 1 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Privacy Journal, 1986 Jan, April (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - R.U.1.2? Queer Community Center, 2006 spring (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Rainbow Multiversity, Inc., 1986 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Reality, Inc., 1985 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Renewal House, Undated (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Resist, Inc., 1983-1991 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Rhode Island Alliance for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights, 1998 March (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Rhode Island Division of Personnel Administration, Personnel pRIde, 1986 February (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Rhode Island Task Force on Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual and Transgender Youth, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - RSVP Travel Productions, Inc., 1987 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Seacoast Gay Men (SGM), Identity, 1999 October (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Senior Action in a Gay Environment (SAGE), Undated (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Servicemembers Legal Defense Fund (SLDF), Undated (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Silent Nature Walk, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Social Justice for Women, Circa 1990 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Sojourner, The Women's Forum, 1998 June (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Southern Vermont Lesbian / Gay Men's Coalition, The Open Closet, 1982-1983 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Speaking for Ourselves, 1991 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Spiritual Needs Workshop, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Stonewall Center, 1995 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Texas Human Rights Foundation (THRF), 1990-1991 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Tri-City Mental Health Services, Inc., 1986 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Tufts University, 1989 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Umoja Group, 1996 June (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Unit Against Rape and Sexual Assault (URSA), Undated (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Unitarian Universalist Legal Ministry, The Parish Advocate, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - United States Department of Health and Human Services, AIDS Clinical Trials, 1989 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Universal Fellowship of Metropolitan Community Churches (UFMCC), 1982, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - University of California San Francisco AIDS Program at San Francisco General Hospital, AIDS File, 1993 December (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - University of Massachusetts Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual Awareness Week, 1988 April (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Valley Gay Alliance (VGA), Gayzette, 1989-1993 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Vermont Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Rights (VCLGR), 1994-1995 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Vermont Department of Health, Undated (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Vermont Freedom to Marry Task Force, 1998 September (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Vermonters for Civil Unions, 1998-2000 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - "What To Do If You're Fired", 1990 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Whitman-Walker Clinic Legal Services, AIDS Advocacy Update, 1999 July (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Woman Vision, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Worcester Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual Pride, 1993 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - World Congress of Gay and Lesbian Jewish Organizations (WCGLJO), Undated (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Women's Bar Association (WBA), 1983-1988 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Youth Committee on the Governor's Commission on Gay and Lesbian Youth, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 15)
- Additional material, Accession 2011-M-026
  - Computer files (Reel 1)
    Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
- Additional material, 1993-2014; Accession 2015-M-007; 4.63; (12 boxes)
  - Development records, 1994-2009
    - Cards
      - New Year's, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Same-sex marriage anniversary
        - First, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 2)
        - Fifth, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Thanksgiving
        - Circa 2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
        - 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
      - Thank you, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
    - Correspondence
      - Happy epistles, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Sample letters, Circa 2000s (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Financial
      - Acquisitions (fundraising)
        - 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
        - 2008 fall (Box 1, Folder 12)
        - 2009 winter (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Budget planning, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Marketing plan, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Park Square Advocates financial statements, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Photographs and videos
      - Connecticut event, Hartford, 2007 May 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Individuals
        - Craig, Amelia, Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, Circa 1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
        - Levi, Jennifer and Germaine Berger (Box 1, Folder 19)
        - Lisa and Trish, event unidentified, Circa 2000s (Box 1, Folder 20)
        - Unidentified male, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Parties, seasonal
        Many are contact sheets.
        - Summer
          - before 2000 (Box 1, Folder 22)
          - 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 23-25)
            Includes some negatives.
          - 2003-2006 (Box 2, Folder 1-4)
        - Winter
          - 2000 (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
          - 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 7-11)
      - Pride march, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 12-13)
        Mostly contact print sheets.
      - Spirit of Justice award dinner
        - Photographs, 2001-2006 (Box 3, Folder 1-6)
        - Videos
          - 2004, 2 (Box 4–5)
          - 2006, 1 (Box 6)
      - Staff photos
        - 2001 (Box 3, Folder 7)
        - 2003 (Box 3, Folder 8)
        - Cunningham, Carisa, contact sheet, Circa 2000s (Box 3, Folder 9)
        - Swislow, Lee, contact sheets, Circa 2000s (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Third Attorney Campaign, Circa 1998 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Victory party celebrating right to marry in Massachusetts, 2003 November (Box 3, Folder 12-14)
        Includes negatives.
      - Washington, D.C. event, unidentified, Probably 2000s (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Women's Dance contact sheets, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Womens' Event, 2002 April 17 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Women's House Party (Elyse Cherrys'), 2001 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Unidentified GLAD event, Circa 2000s (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Publicity information, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Executive director records, 1993-2014
    - General administrative files
      - 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - 2008-2014 (Box 7, Folder 2-3)
    - Board of directors
      - Board affairs, 2004-2014 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Donors, memoranda, budget, 2000-2004 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - "GLAD Board of Directors - Who Are We?", 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Budget for 2004, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Diversity
      - General, 2001-2010 (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
      - "GLAD Diversity Assessment Report of Findings", 2008 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Staff, 2013-2014 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Executive director transition planning, 2011-2013 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - HIV, 2010-2013 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Human resources (HR) consultancy, 2011-2013 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Lobbyist reporting statements, campaign contributions, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Marriage equality
      - Children issue, 2008-2009 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Defense of Marriage Act (DOMA)
        - General, 2007-2013 (Box 8, Folder 11)
        - Civil unions, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 12)
        - District court hearing, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 1)
        - Supreme Court of the United States (SCOTUS) strategic planning, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Geographical
        Material is primarily concerned with right to marry but other initiatives may also be referenced.
        - Regional
          - New England Initiatives, 2008-2009 (Box 9, Folder 3)
        - State
          - Maine, 2005-2012 (Box 9, Folder 4-8)
          - Massachusetts, Mass Equality, 2004-2010 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
          - New Hampshire
            - General, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 3)
            - Bedford v. New Hampshire Technical College, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 4)
          - Rhode Island, 2006-2012 (Box 11, Folder 1-3)
      - Marriage of same-sex couples, Boston, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Marriage-related bills, 2000-2009 (Box 11, Folder 5-6)
      - National meeting, 2010-2011 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - National work - marriage, 2011-2012 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Religion issue, 2006-2008 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - 1913 Decision Day protocol, draft, 2006 February 10 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Rebellious lawyering, 1993, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Retreats, 2005-2013 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Strategic direction, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Strategic operations, 2005-2007 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Strategic planning, 2004-2011 (Box 12, Folder 6-7)
    - Technology assessment, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Transgender health insurance, 2013-2014 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Transgender Rights Project (TRP), 2005-2009 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - United States v. Windsor, notes and schedules, 2013 March (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Youth, 2005-2012 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Computer files (Box 13)
    - DICKIEDESIGN.com 003_flourish003 114 Franklin Street Stoneham, MA, 02180 USA, 2015-M-007-0001; 1 (Box 13)
    - GLAD Dance Poster, 2015-M-007-0002; 1 (Box 13)
    - GLAD Program dickiedesign.com, 2015-M-007-0003; 1 (Box 13)
    - GLAD Spirit of Justice Program, 2015-M-007-0004; 1 (Box 13)
    - CT event 2007, 2015-M-007-0005; 1 (Box 13)
    - Spirit of Justice Award Tribute Use with honoree in attendence Barataria Productions Contact: Michael Eldridge, 2015-M-007-0006; 1 (Box 13)
    - Spirit of Justice Award Tribute Use if honoree absent Barataria productions Contact: Michael Eldridge, 2015-M-007-0007; 1 (Box 13)
    - GLAD Spirit of Justice 2006 Susan Symonds Main Frame Photographics, 2015-M-007-0008; 1 (Box 13)
    - GLAD Spirit of Justice '05 Web Images, 2015-M-007-0009; 1 (Box 13)
    - 04 Spirit of Justice Presentations, 2015-M-007-0010; 1 (Box 13)
    - Summer Party 2005 GLAD, 2015-M-007-0011; 1 (Box 13)
    - GLAD Jennifer Levi, 2001 ©Mainframe Photographics Please give photo credit, 2015-M-007-0012; 1 (Box 13)
    - Mainframe Photographics 2003 All Rights Reserved GLAD Dance 2003, 2015-M-007-0013; 1 (Box 13)
    - Ads and photos from Dickie Design 10/03, 2015-M-007-0014; 1 (Box 13)
    - Mainframe Photo ©2005 GLAD winter party 2005, 2015-M-007-0015; 1 (Box 13)
    - © Mainframe Photographics GLAD Plaintiff Couples Photo credit must be given, 2015-M-007-0016; 1 (Box 13)
    - GLAD winter party 2004 Mainframe Photo ©, 2015-M-007-0017; 1 (Box 13)
    - Mainframe Photographics ©2003 GLAD Winter Party 2003, 2015-M-007-0018; 1 (Box 13)
    - [No label on CD-R. Label on jewel case] Jon Smac Photo Copywrite Summer Party 2001, 2015-M-007-0019; 1 (Box 13)
    - SOJ '07 -Chris, 2015-M-007-0020; 1 (Box 13)
    - GLAD 617-426-1350 In honor of your birthday Peter Hogan, 2015-M-007-0021; 1 (Box 13)
    - No label on disc. Post it note label: Ellen 2 DVDs to test (We should test in the Reg DVD player & computer) -AJ, 2015-M-007-0022; 1 (Box 13)
    - GLAD Awards Stephen M. Mindich PTOWN, July 28, 2007, 2015-M-007-0023; 1 (Box 13)
    - SOJ 2007 Dinner, 2015-M-007-0024; 1 (Box 13)
    - Morning Ed. Court Reform 3/5/03, 2015-M-007-0025; 1 (Box 13)
- Additional material, 1975-1999; Accession 2015-M-014
  Materials in this series pertain to Bragdon v. Abbott, which was the first court case concerning the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA) to be heard by the United States Supreme Court, as well as the first case involving HIV to be heard by the court. The case originated in Bangor, Maine in 1994, when dentist Randon Bragdon refused to treat Sidney Abbott at his practice after Abbott disclosed that she was HIV positive. GLAD filed suit on Abbott's behalf in federal district court in Maine in 1995, asserting that Abbott's HIV positive status qualified as a disability, and that Bragdon's refusal of service qualified as discrimination under the ADA. GLAD won this case, known as Abbott v. Bragdon, after which Bragdon's attorneys appealed the decision at the First Circuit Court of Appeals in Boston, where GLAD also won. Bragdon ultimately appealed to the United States Supreme Court, which ruled 5-4 in Abbott's favor in 1998. Materials documenting the case include correspondence, news clippings, memos, background research materials, notes, depositions, briefs, summary judgements, court decisions, and reports.
  - Molinari, John (1 of 2), 1988-1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Molinari, John (2 of 2), 1988-1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Expert report: Randon Bragdon, 1995 May (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bragdon Deposition Part 2, 1995 June (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Expert report: Donald Craven, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Curriculum Vitae: Donald Craven, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Expert report: Deborah Greenspan, 1995 August (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Expert report: Donald Marianos, 1995 June (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Expert report: John Molinari, 1995 June (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Supplemental expert report: John Molinari, 1995 June (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Curriculum Vitae: John Molinari, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)